hokagestore.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to Hokage Store and any of its affiliated websites, applications and other digital services in connection with which this Privacy Policy is linked or posted (collectively, “Services”). 

This Privacy Policy explains how Hokage Store collects and uses data and information that may identify or can be directly associated with an individual person (“Personal Information”). Hokage Store respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains Hokage Store’s policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of any information we receive including your Personal Information (if any).

Hokage Store provides anime-themed goods, that can be distributed and offered on the website hokagestore.com.

## **Information Hokage Store Collects from Users**

Hokage Store uses services to collect information regarding Users’ activities and operations that interact with the website hokagestore.com. Such information might include IP-address, Session ID, browser type, mobile or desktop ID, referrer, phone numbers, emails, addresses, names, order details, method of payment, feedback or answers provided by the User to any interactive content unit made available with the website. Such information may qualify as Personal Information in some Users’ jurisdictions, however, we do not make any use of such data to directly identify individuals or to associate it with individuals.

We may collect Personal Data when you interact with Hokage Store, such as when you:

  * Purchase, return merchandise at our store
  * Consent to receive our promotional email
  * Visit our site;
  * Consent to our use of cookies;
  * Participate in our contests or promotions;
  * Consent to the collection and processing of your location data;
  * Contact our Customer Service

## **How Hokage Store Protects Information**

Hokage Store follows applicable laws and generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to Hokage Store by implementing adequate technical and organizational protection measures, both during transmission and once Hokage Store receives it. These measures will be continuously adjusted and updated in accordance with current industry standards. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while Hokage Store strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect Personal Information, Hokage Store cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## **How Hokage Store Uses Information**

Hokage Store will not share your Personal Data with third party controllers (i.e. third parties that use the Personal Data for their own purposes). Hokage Store will only disclose Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy or where required by law, regulation, subpoena or court order; we will only process, use or share User’s Personal Information with third parties with User’s explicit permission. Hokage Store uses Personal Information to the extent necessary for internal purposes – for example, in connection with offering the Services, to provide Users with advertising that Hokage Store reasonably believes may be useful or interesting to the User. In addition, by analyzing all information Hokage Store receives, including all information concerning Users and their interaction with the website hokagestore.com, Hokage Store may irreversibly compile aggregated statistical information. Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be improved and tailored to customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and does not, in and of itself, identify any specific end user or customer of Hokage Store. Hokage Store may share such Statistical Information with its partners or any third party, without restriction, on commercial terms that Hokage Store can determine in its sole discretion.

Personal Information is not transferred or disclosed to third parties other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## **Opt-Out**

If User does not wish its Personal Information to be collected, processed or shared for the above purposes, he may opt out from this use with effect for the future. For opting out, the End User can do so by sending an email to [support@hokagestore.com](mailto:support@hokagestore.com) (we do encourage you to reach out via email which is checked more often).

## **Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to the User’s browser and stored on his computer or mobile device. All cookies used by Hokage Store are persistent cookies, i.e. they will be stored on the User’s device after the browser session has expired. Any cookie will be deleted within one month after it has been placed unless configured otherwise. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but the User can change this setting so his browser either refuses all cookies or informs him when a cookie is being sent. Also, the User is free to delete any existing cookies at any time with future effect. Some features of Hokage Store’s Services may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.

Cookies placed on Users’ computers:

Cookies placed on an User’s computer will transmit the User’s Personal Information as specified above to Hokage Store for the purposes also specified above.

## **Marketing Communications**

We may send you email or other messages about us or our products and services. By the Privacy Policy or using the Services, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages. You can ask to have your Personal Information removed from our mailing list and stop receiving future communication from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at support@hokagestore.com. You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email or other message we send. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions using the Services without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account.

## **User’s Rights**

User may at any time request information from Hokage Store regarding his Personal Information stored at Hokage Store, its origin, recipients or categories of recipients the data has been transferred to and the purpose of storage.

Upon written request by User Hokage Store will make all commercially reasonable efforts to delete any information provided to it, unless required otherwise for further execution of an agreement with a Customer or required by applicable laws. Hokage Store cannot restore information that it has deleted.

For executing any of these rights User may contact Hokage Store by sending an email to support@hokagestore.com, and we do encourage you to reach out via email which is checked more often.

## **Changes**

Hokage Store may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If required under applicable law, we will provide you with written notice of our changes. We will not make changes that have a material retroactive effect unless we are legally required to do so. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of the amended policy. The amended policy supersede all previous versions, notices or statements of or about the policy.

## **Comments and Questions / Contact Information**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at  support@hokagestore.com.
